(This program contains indirect advertisements.)
(The Mullae-dong sky has cleared after the rain.)
- Have you been well?
- I have. Have you?
Yes. Should we speak casually to each other, Hyeong Seo?
- Yes, please do, Kyung Pyo.
- Okay.
- Let's both do.
- Shall we?
- Come on.
- That'd be better, right?
- What?
You're so much older than me.
- Why?
- Are you not?
I was born in 1990.
Am I much older?
- It doesn't matter these days.
- You're eight years older...
- Yes, you're right.
- Yes, it doesn't matter these days.
- People these days all...
- It's just...
I'm worried that I'll forget my manners...
if I start speaking casually to you.
That's fine.
- Shall we, then?
- That's fine.
Okay, Kyung Pyo.
Yes, that's nice.
(They've grown a bit closer.)
- Hello.
- She's here.
- Hi, Kyung Pyo.
- Hello, ma'am.
- Oh, my.
What are you two doing?
- Hey, are we the mafia?
- Hello, ma'am.
(A mafia-like greeting?)
- At rest.
- Yes.
(At rest.)
- Have you been well?
- Yes, I have.
- Yes, of course.
Did you tan a bit, Hyeong Seo?
- You're nice and bronzy.
- Right, you're a bit...
Really? Did I tan a bit?
Did you not do anything?
I didn't get a tan.
I just don't wear sunscreen much.
- That's not good.
- But I'm an outdoors person.
- I see.
- An outdoors person.
She must be from a new gang.
The outdoors gang.
(Hello, I'm BIBI from the Outdoors Gang.)
In a moment, someone from the Indoors Gang will be here.
The Indoors Gang.
- Someone who hates summers...
- Yes.
Hello.
- Hello.
- The Indoors Gang is here.
- Come here, Indoors Gang.
- Yes.
Oh, someone is coming today.
Yes, today...
- We have two seats ready.
- Yes, they're coming.
So today, we...
Oh, you really parted your hair right down the middle.
Yes, I did.
I dressed up a bit. Nice and neat.
- Is that so?
- Nice and neat.
- "One and a Half" vibes?
- Yes.
I see.
- The hair from the heyday of idols.
- That's right.
- Like when Sechs Kies debuted.
- It's really annoying.
You're right.
- Like SECHSKIES...
- Moon Hee Joon...
- You're right.
- or Hee Joon.
Or Uhm Jung Hwa when she did "Eyes."
(It's the style from that general era.)
(Suddenly acting seductive)
- I have felt it for a long time - Why are you singing it?
It's just the morning, and I'm already tired.
(This is my joy.)
How have you been, BIBI?
I've been well.
- Really?
- I have,
- but the production team called me.
- What did they say?
They said we would have pretty intense people next time...
and that I should make sure not to be swayed by them.
- They warned me.
- They said that?
We shot with BIBI last time.
- BIBI seems like a strong person, - Yes.
- but she's not really.
- She's not.
- You're right.
She calls herself a Chihuahua.
- In what way?
- She barks easily...
because she gets scared easily.
(Woof!)
(Suddenly barking)
You didn't need to do that.
(We didn't know she was an actual Chihuahua...)
- I saw that side of you.
- Yes.
But today, I'll be bold.
(Screaming)
What did they...
(Screaming out of nowhere)
What did they say to you...
- Oh, so they...
- What did you say?
(It's only the second shoot, and BIBI has become crazy...)
You go first. The pretty one should go first.
Why? You have such a YCC face right now.
- YCC?
- YCC.
- Do I?
- I love places like that.
- Why?
- Because it's hip.
Oh, they're here.
- Are they?
- I got a glance.
(Such strong auras)
Oh, my.
You said, "Oh, my."
- Are you happy I'm here?
- They're here.
- Hello.
- Welcome.
- Are you happy I'm here?
- Hello.
- Oh, my.
- It's been so long, Jeong An.
- Hello.
- Oh, Na Eun's dad!
- Na Eun's dad.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hello.
(The original techno queen that dominated the 2000s)
(An actress who can become any character)
(A naturally funny variety show star)
(The actress who has everything, Chae Jeong An)
(From SHARP, makers of the best hit songs)
(To a solo artist with many great songs)
(Now the mom of two beautiful princesses)
(Everyone's witty and charming older sister)
(Lee Ji Hye)
- I love this.
- They dominated the 2000s.
- She's still popular today.
- She's a member of SHARP.
By the way, aren't you two very close?
- We met each other before marriage.
- Before marriage.
- I see.
- Yes.
They're clubbing buddies.
- It's karaoke.
- They're karaoke buddies.
(Karaoke buddies instead of clubbing buddies?)
- Karaoke buddies.
- Karaoke buddies?
You know where the word "karaoke" comes from?
- Fake orchestra.
- Oh, my. I see.
- Actually...
Back then, there were so many...
- karaoke bars in Cheongdam-dong.
- There were so many.
That was a time...
when a lot of people went...
- to karaoke often.
- That's right.
That's not where we met.
We actually met in the restroom at a broadcasting station.
- Did you almost get into a fight?
- Is that right?
No, I mean...
Did one of you say...
- "come outside?"
- I don't always get into fights.
- So that's not what happened?
- No.
I went to the restroom,
and I saw a beautiful woman there.
You know how you can feel...
someone's energy when you see them?
I thought that I could become friends with her.
That day, she asked me to go to karaoke with her.
- Right.
- What year was that?
It was 2000.
- That was 26 years ago.
- Or was it 1999?
No, it was 2000.
I was a 1st album singer, and she was a 2nd album singer.
She was number one on the charts.
(1st album singer, Jeong An, Number 1 singer, Ji Hye)
- Actually...
- You were very popular.
I was slightly more established...
at that time.
I wanted to become closer to the number one singer,
so I was kind to her in the restroom.
The drinks are here.
- Is this with lots of caffeine?
- Yes.
- That's for Kyung Pyo.
- It has a lot of caffeine.
Usually around this time of day,
wouldn't you still be in bed?
I'm usually up, but I came back from Japan late last night.
I see. You need to get over the jet lag.
Jet lag?
- Jeong An.
- Yes?
You were probably joking,
but there's no time difference between here and Japan.
I know, but that's not the case with China.
- There's a time difference there.
- One hour.
- Right.
- I found out recently.
We can't exactly call one hour...
- That's true.
- a time difference.
But meal times are important.
What kind of conversation is this?
Anyone listening would think that I really don't know.
I know there's no time difference.
I was there last month.
- Where?
- Tokyo. Ginza.
What did you do there?
I went shopping.
(Her way of speaking is strangely charming.)
That's great.
What is today's theme?
The theme of today's second episode is...
The Owner Who's Serious About "Mi."
- What?
- "Mi?"
- "Mi" that means taste?
- What?
- It could also mean beautiful.
- Is it beautiful or taste?
- We don't know which one it is.
- "Mi" could also mean rice.
That's right.
- My gosh.
- Rice.
That's amazing.
Is that a hint for today?
We tried this...
for the first time last week.
We were very surprised last week.
Yes, it was very surprising.
They're cassette tapes.
B-Side is the theme of the show this season.
(Important clues of on-site audio from each of the three places)
We have to listen to these carefully.
These will be hints.
We got it right last time during the first episode.
- Yes.
- We almost got it wrong,
but BIBI was very sharp.
- So you're sharp.
- She convinced us otherwise.
You gave it to me because it was my first time.
- No.
- No, we had no idea.
She definitely looks like the smartest one here.
- Really?
- I agree.
What do you think about me?
I need some time to get to know you.
(The longer you look, the prettier he gets.)
- Let's listen to it.
- Okay.
It's the first one.
(First store, a clue from the on-site reaction)
- Encore - Encore
- One more song - One more song
"One more song?"
"Encore, encore, one more song."
- What?
- Right?
(What does it have to do with "mi?")
It's related to music.
After saying encore,
- they said, "One more song."
- Right.
- Yes.
- Is it related to concerts?
All right, this is the second one.
(Let's listen to the clue from the second location.)
(Second store, a clue from the on-site reaction)
Cooking is complete.
Is parking complete?
- Cooking.
- Cooking is complete.
It's the sound of a rice cooker.
- This is...
- It's like the one at my house.
- a classic rice cooker sound.
- Right.
- It said, "Cook, cook, cooking."
- Yes.
Rice "mi" could be the answer.
Right.
This is the third and the last one.
(Third store, a clue from the on-site reaction)
(Groaning)
Bubbles...
- It's bubbling.
- A yawn?
- "Bubbles..."
- "Bubbles?"
Why are there bubbles?
- Bubbles?
- Bubbles are rising?
What comes to mind is a performance.
Something that disappears after being very popular.
The completed cooking represents the peak of popularity.
The bubbles represent that popularity fading away.
Could that be the story?
- I think you're wrong about that.
- Am I?
- Are they not connected?
- No.
They're not connected. They're all separate.
Ji Hye, they're separate.
(The creative genius)
- That was nice.
- It captures the rise...
and fall of something.
But it actually made sense.
- I agree.
- She was so confident about it.
- I pretended to know everything.
- It's okay.
I was just being enthusiastic. Should I tone it down a little?
Should I tone it down?
- You're doing fine.
- I don't mind.
If you tell me to, I'll tone it down right away.
- Just give me the word.
- You'd tone it down if we ask?
Definitely.
She's incredibly flexible.
- She's very...
- He knows me accurately.
- Right.
- She's very flexible.
- I can do anything you ask.
- I know.
Let's get going.
- Shall we go now?
- I'm curious.
The weather is so beautiful.
This is the definition of sunny weather.
(The weather that makes you want to walk around Mullae-dong)
It's nice to walk around on a day like today.
This is what Mullae-dong is originally like.
- Right.
- These metalworking shops...
- Metalworking...
This place has...
many of these small metalworking shops.
- Hello.
A lot of inventions were made in this neighborhood.
- Right.
- In Mullae-dong,
- They could make anything.
- they could make everything.
- Right.
- Yes.
These days,
there are many small cafes...
and little restaurants here.
- It's a trendy area.
- It's very hip these days.
Right.
"Scissorhands?"
My goodness.
Gosh. Hello, sir.
Sir...
"Air conditioning fully equipped?" That's hilarious.
- "Air conditioning fully equipped."
- Hello.
- He looks amazing.
- I love your hairstyle.
- Your hairstyle...
Are you the owner of the barbershop?
- Yes.
- Your hairstyle is amazing.
Seriously.
You have so much hair on both sides.
Sir, you have so much hair.
- You have a lot of hair.
- Most of my hair on top is gone.
But your styling is so cool.
- We'll get going.
- You look amazing.
It's heartwarming to see "air conditioning fully equipped."
- It's like a neighborhood hangout.
- Right.
- Have a good day.
- Goodbye.
- Back in the day, - Yes?
there weren’t that many air conditioners.
People put up signs outside saying,
- Right.
- "Air conditioning fully equipped."
- It's hot in the summer.
- It was the neighborhood hangout.
Because of the hot weather.
What?
- Is this the place?
- Is this it?
What's this?
- Gosh, this is...
- Is this the first place?
What?
"Run by mom and her son?"
(Run by mom and her son)
It looks like it's been photoshopped.
Since we're questioning everything,
- doesn't it look AI-generated?
- Right, it does.
(An AI-generated photo by the production crew?)
Isn't this Car, the Garden?
Maybe Car, the Garden opened this place.
It has that vibe.
Gosh, this is...
(They go inside Car, the Garden's place.)
Is this the first store?
What?
(Looking carefully)
It feels very cool inside.
(At first glance, it looks like an ordinary restaurant.)
What's this?
Oh, my.
- Beef tripe?
- My gosh.
(Flapping)
I love beef tripe.
Me too.
- That sounds delicious.
- I really love beef tripe.
- I'm a huge fan of beef tripe.
- Let's sit here.
It'll be so delicious.
(What's this place that will drive beef tripe fans crazy?)
(A beef tripe restaurant tucked away in a quiet alley in Mullae)
This is...
what the owner mentioned earlier.
An Owner Who's Serious About "Mi."
"One more song."
- "Encore, one more song."
- Encore - Encore
- One more song - One more song
(What could these sounds be hinting at)
- "Encore."
- Will the owner sing for us?
Did the owner sing?
There was a photo of Car, the Garden in the front.
- What?
- So the vibe...
- I saw him in the photo.
- Right.
Even the menu has these wavy marks...
like it's singing.
Half, half, assorted platter
We were really surprised...
during the first episode.
- We were very surprised.
- Why?
There were hidden clues everywhere.
(B-Side: The opposite side of A-side)
(The hidden side beyond what we can see)
(The hidden answer beyond what we can see)
(Last week)
- What?
- Goodness.
(B-Side with 100 citizens)
(The people they met on the streets were carrying...)
(the crucial clues to what was fake.)
(Wait a minute.)
(This isn't B-Side, is it?)
(Everything is a B-Side clue.)
(Question everything you encounter)
(What kind of B-Side will be hidden today?)
- Really? I must look carefully.
- We have to look carefully.
We need to take a good look at this restaurant,
so shall we call the owner?
- Sir?
(A musical intro playing from somewhere)
- There it is.
- Hello.
He's going to sing.
My goodness.
(Suddenly, someone appears on the monitor.)
I'm Kim Kkot, the owner of the beef tripe restaurant.
I'll sing a song for you.
- What?
- My gosh.
(A song all of a sudden?)
("0+0" by Hanroro)
He's good.
(The owner's very own special menu)
(One song sung from the kitchen)
(I won't abandon you)
(I won't)
(Singing)
(His emotional performance quickly gets them misty-eyed.)
I like those high notes.
(It hits the spot for the top 100 listeners.)
(With the first-row experience at the beef tripe restaurant,)
(it's prepped and grilled.)
(Are you crying?)
I didn't think I'd listen to HANRORO at a beef tripe place.
I know, right?
(The restaurant owner's monitor appears out of nowhere.)
- The owner is a great singer.
- Right?
- I was surprised.
- He has a vibe.
(Cheering)
- Hi.
Hi.
I also see Oh Chang Suk in him.
- Exactly.
- Go Chang Suk.
Right, Go Chang Suk.
- Call me Tripe Chang Suk.
- Tripe Chang Suk?
- Tripe Chang Suk.
(Tripe Chang Suk, not Go Chang Suk)
I'm Mullae-dong Beard RORO.
- Beard-RORO?
- Beard-RORO.
That's right. I've got many nicknames.
Is there a reason you started singing while serving food?
The business I ran before this one went completely bankrupt.
I went through a tough time.
- I see.
- It was depressing.
When my wife and I visited Namhae,
- I sang at a park.
- Right.
People gathered around, clapping and cheering me on.
- It was...
- It made you happy...
- and gave you comfort.
- Yes, it gave me comfort.
"People enjoy it," I thought to myself.
That's how all of this started.
(Fueled by the power of music,)
(he opened a restaurant where he sings for customers.)
My restaurant serves mellow beef tripe.
It's also a unique restaurant where I perform live...
with a groove.
I turned my singing into a menu.
It's called the beef tripe song.
If a customer orders one, they submit a song request.
Some even write the story behind it...
and hand it to me.
I read their requests and sing the song.
(With the owner's personal emotional touch,)
(it became a hit with Gen Z.)
(Social media response has skyrocketed.)
Sixth Sense crew,
is this place real?
The owner here is obsessed with the Mi in Do-Re-Mi.
(The first restaurant)
- His singing, you know?
- Yes.
- What's written on your apron.
- Yes?
Is it embroidered, not just written?
Yes, it's embroidered.
These are the songs requested by my customers.
That's why the fonts are different.
Correct.
I had them all embroidered.
(Traces of different handwriting)
So the handwriting doesn't come off even after washing?
(The owner wants to keep the memories of his customers forever.)
That's so moving.
(Tearing up)
How many songs do you sing a day?
A day...
Jeong An sure knows how to ask.
On busy days, I sometimes sing 20 to 30 songs.
- On slower days, around ten.
- He sings twice as many songs...
- as I would in a two-hour concert.
- Twice the amount.
I sing every day.
That's incredible.
I might have seen him in a video.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
It was probably Instagram.
That angle from above his head.
- Does it look familiar?
- Yes, that angle looks familiar.
With that, I got the feeling this place is real.
Isn't the place we're currently seeing the kitchen?
That itself is a brilliant idea.
Either way, here's the important part.
- The menu.
- Yes.
- What should we try?
- Right.
We have a menu called...
- the beef tripe platter.
- What?
- That sounds good.
- Yes, that one.
Pizza.
It's a menu that combines...
pane gopchang and green onion makchang.
(Impressed)
(Laughing)
BIBI was like...
(A terrible reenactment)
(My appetite is on another level!)
- That sounds amazing.
- She's loving it.
- She loves food.
- I do.
- It's good.
- Great.
If you write down a song request,
- The beef tripe song.
- I'll sing while you eat.
Okay.
If you write down 3 to 4 songs,
I'll sing one I know.
Here's what I want to listen to.
- It was written on his apron.
- I see.
"My Whole World."
- "My Whole World."
- I love that song.
You're getting teary just from the song title.
I don't know what's up with me.
The title itself is already heart-wrenching.
- You're a feeler, right?
- You must be a feeler.
Bringing it up was...
What's wrong? This isn't the last episode.
It must be because I'm hungry.
- Is it because you're hungry?
- Let's get her some food.
And "Heartless" by Chae Jeong An.
- Jeong An's songs are nice.
- They have fun beats.
(Added "Heartless" by Chae Jeong An,)
(completing the beef tripe song request)
He's cooking now.
- You can see him in real time.
- Right.
- My gosh.
- Being able to see...
- everything while eating...
- It's like live streaming.
- helps build trust.
- True.
(Let's get to grilling the beef tripe.)
Wouldn't beef tripe become more popular?
(Hoping beef tripe would go global)
That's how I came up with the beef tripe platter.
(The owner's ambitious menu)
(To the pre-grilled beef tripe,)
(he adds a secret sauce to boost the smoky flavor!)
As for pane gopchang, I add the gopchang to bread.
You mix in the cheese and have it with bread.
As for the green onion makchang, it's like Japanese negi makchang.
You make a wrap out of the green onion,
makchang, and teriyaki sauce.
Those two foods make up the platter.
(This is the beef tripe platter.)
It's a menu that expands Korean cuisine into...
Western and Japanese cuisine.
Here's your order.
Oh, my.
- Is this the platter?
- Yes, it is.
- My gosh.
- It looks good.
The pane is a pig's face.
It's a pig's face viewed from above.
The pane?
- These are the ears.
- The ears and face.
- Correct.
- How cute.
Incredible. Thank you.
(The plating showcases the owner's creativity.)
I was going to eat in moderation today.
But I won't be able to.
There's no moderation here.
Place it on top.
Place a piece of gopchang on top.
Like so.
- Separately.
- Separately?
- Yes.
- I see.
(Taking a bite)
Look at the cheese.
It's giving off rice cake vibes.
Is this gopchang?
(Smiling)
- How is it?
- It doesn't smell meaty at all.
(Packed with smoky flavors without a meaty smell)
(Impossible to let go of)
- It's good.
It's really good.
- Right?
- This menu alone must attract...
a lot of customers.
(A flavor that drives views)
It's a classic example of today's food trends.
The gopchang sauce is delicious.
In other words, the food isn't tailored to us.
(Crying)
We've got some oldies here, don't we?
- Who?
- I won't say who.
- The ratio would be four to...
How cold of you.
Four to...
(I'm not one of the oldies.)
Everyone, are you enjoying the food?
- Yes!
It's time for the beef tripe song.
I'm going to sing a song you've requested.
- Which one will he sing?
- May I?
- Yes.
- Go ahead.
Thank you.
How could I pass up the chance to sing a song by the beautiful...
Chae Jeong An, who's here today?
Here's "Heartless" by Chae Jeong An.
Please enjoy.
(It's my song.)
"Heartless."
I didn't think I'd get to hear it here.
("Heartless" by Chae Jeong An)
This song gets you pumped up.
(Cheering)
I love it.
(Speaking of "Heartless...")
(Shaking up late-1990s Korea,)
(a techno warrior appeared.)
(Let's go back 30 years!)
(Take me with you!)
(In a trance)
(Singing)
Listen to that ad-lib!
(I did everything you wanted me to)
(I didn't do anything you hated)
Your!
Isn't that the original key?
(The original techno queen is here.)
(Whether I love you or not!)
(Getting excited)
(This is so much fun.)
(I could tell even if you played innocent)
(Bold and sexy)
(Husky)
(The love is beyond comprehension.)
You two have good chemistry.
(Dancing the day away)
(The perfect partner)
(Cheering)
(Tripe Chang Suk is beyond amazing.)
He's good.
Thank you. That was the beef tripe song.
(The owner leaves.)
It's nice to hear it again after so long.
- It's a masterpiece, right?
- Yes, it is.
(He acknowledges "Heartless.")
Really, it's a masterpiece.
- Of course.
- It's a fun song.
I saw Ji Hye from the 2000s again after so long.
For a good while, her life was all about...
"Tae Ri."
True.
- It brought back memories.
- Right?
- It did.
- You went to Ppeokkugi, right?
Ppeokkugi and Switch It Up.
Hearing that helped me remember the name.
What kind of beer snacks did you like?
I used to go for meat.
I liked Lord Park's.
You went to places...
that were quite pricey.
I liked people who were a little well off.
(Deeply touching)
I was broke.
I wanted the others to be well off.
- I can totally relate to that.
- Right?
Jae Seok was penniless,
so he asked the others for a ride to nightclubs.
- Those were the days.
- Yes.
- That's unexpected.
- How so?
- I didn't think you went clubbing.
I loved going to nightclubs.
- Don't you know...
- That's new.
Nallari Yu Jae Seok?
- Nallari Yu Jae Seok.
- Nallari.
It was such a fun time.
You know that thing at nightclubs.
- Matchmaking?
- Yes, matchmaking. That system.
System. Yes, the system.
- System.
- The matchmaking system.
Personally, I want it to return.
It's nice.
Listen, BIBI. That system existed,
but some people never experienced it.
(Not everyone could enjoy the matchmaking system.)
(Solemn)
"Where are they going?"
"Why are they leaving and heading over there?"
I always saw them leave and stayed where I always was.
(But I remained exactly where I was.)
That's why Eun I's table never got robbed.
I watched everyone's bags.
I watched them all.
- The safe zone.
- I watched all the bags.
- Of course.
- There were no thefts.
This feels like a drinking party.
- You're right.
- It's fun.
This all started with "Heartless."
Totally.
- You're right.
- The owner singing "Heartless..."
- was a trip down memory lane.
- Yes.
- I get the power of songs now.
- For real.
(Applauding)
- This place is...
- Really.
This is Sixth Sense.
We're enjoying ourselves a little too much...
as if this place were actually real.
- For real.
- Right.
Shouldn't we...
- There's not an ounce of doubt.
- No.
Actually, if you think about it carefully,
if the production crew wanted to install that,
they totally could have.
True.
- All they needed was a kitchen.
- All they needed was a kitchen...
to install the monitor and all.
(This place is fake!)
(The production crew installed the sound equipment?)
I find it weird that the floor isn't greasy.
- Exactly.
- Right?
- The floor isn't greasy at all.
- Beef tripe places are...
- usually greasy.
- It's greasy.
(The tripe place has a surprisingly spotless, grease-free floor.)
- It's...
- This one is quite tough.
- Got it. Next.
- Okay.
- Let's find Mi.
- Mi.
(The Singing Do-Re-Mi Owner)
(A tripe place with no grease on the floor)
- It's not easy.
- No, it isn't.
- Last week,
we got it right out of pure luck.
Last week's scale was on a different level.
- Totally.
- Yes.
- There were too many cast members.
- Around...
What's more, all 100 citizens we met...
were cast members chosen by our production crew.
(Surprised)
- Really?
- It was no joke.
This show is like a blockbuster.
- It's "The Trulyman Show."
- Right?
I agree.
It's "The Truman Show," not "The Trulyman Show."
Gosh.
(Oh, no!)
I thought she said it on purpose.
Did you just cuss?
I classify the traits of people who make others laugh...
into three categories.
Jeong An is one of them.
No matter what she does,
people find it funny.
(Is that so?)
(Living proof)
- I have this weird obsession.
- What is it?
Because I have this great urge to be funny,
I don't laugh when others are...
- being funny.
- You don't laugh.
- No.
- Are you the envious type?
Rather than that, I compete against them all by myself.
I get it.
It's just...
- But...
- Do you think to yourself,
"Why didn't I say that?"
Let go of the need to compete so much.
- Relax.
- I competed against you...
in the past,
but you were better than me.
Are you acknowledging it?
Are you accepting defeat?
- But you're prettier.
- No.
- Let me be funny.
- Your beauty...
has caught up quite a lot.
- Is that so? Have I made progress?
- Yes, we're slightly on par.
- Really?
- Nice.
Ji Hye has an area where she's outstanding.
Her crying while smiling.
- When it comes to acting...
- It's second to none.
- No one can match it.
- I wonder if you all saw it.
(Crying)
(Surprised)
(Wiping her tears)
(Here's the Korean Joker.)
(Crying while smiling)
- Is this Ji Hye?
- Yes, keep watching.
- Really?
- She's sad from the breakup.
- Seriously?
- Yes.
- I know that video.
- Have you already watched it?
- Wasn't it hilarious?
- I didn't know it was Ji Hye.
Ji Hye has such a baby face now.
Why were you so...
- Do I look better now?
- She looks like your daughter.
- Really.
- Does that mean I'm Tae Ri?
(Guess who is older!)
- You look that young.
- Am I Moon Tae Ri?
- How funny.
- I'm serious.
BIBI is adorable.
- Totally.
- Thank you.
You have a baby face, Ji Hye.
What's wrong with you?
- What's wrong with you?
- You're younger than me, right?
(A killer blow: You're younger than me, right?)
- What?
- Yes, I am.
I like her. I like BIBI.
I'd better keep in touch.
- BIBI is amazing.
- I love it.
- Yes, she is.
- BIBI stole my heart.
- Right.
- Really,
that remark was incredible.
- We should take note of it.
- For real.
- Shall we get off?
- Shall we?
Thank you, sir.
(Who is the Mi-loving second owner?)
- Ji Hye.
- The apricots look good.
Mi for rice is here!
- What?
- Mi.
- Restaurant Mi.
- Yes, Mi.
- You're right, but...
- Mi.
What was the second tape that we listened to?
It was the...
The sound of a rice cooker.
("Cooking is complete" went on repeat.)
(As BIBI deduced,)
(is the second Mi for rice?)
Shall we go inside?
(Jae Seok steps into the restaurant first.)
What?
(He discovered something.)
Over here.
- What is it?
- Rice...
What's wrong?
(Surprised)
Does this place specialize in rice?
(What can be surprising about rice?)
Each region's rice is cooked separately.
I smell rice.
- A restaurant specializing in rice.
- Amazing.
(From the entrance,)
(it looks like a normal restaurant.)
(Walk to the side,)
(and rice cookers are lined up!)
Ten?
(There are 10 rice cookers!)
(Dalhami, Hangyeolmi, Yudel, Songhyangmi, short-grain,)
(Goun, Banggeut, Yeonjin, Gawaji 1, Jungwonjinmi)
The place is filled with the smell of rice. I love it.
They only use Korean rice.
It's a restaurant specializing in rice.
(Is this place real?)
I smell something savory.
The smell of rice is so nice.
- Guys.
- This one here is short-grain rice.
Goun rice, Yeonjin rice,
- Hangyeolmi rice, and Dalhami rice.
- Look.
Here are the flavor, aroma, gloss, and stickiness levels.
(Detailed descriptions of each type of rice)
Even side dishes that pair well with each rice.
Oh, my. This is amazing.
(Even side dish recommendations paired with each rice!)
Is it that you can choose which rice you want to eat?
This is a first for me.
Rice comes in a number of varieties.
(Happily browsing the restaurant)
My mouth is watering.
(These two are in serious detective mode.)
The rice cooker model is too new.
- Right?
- I went rice cooker shopping...
- while moving house.
- Guys.
The thing is...
- Right?
- The rice cookers are too new.
- What?
- Too new.
- They are too new.
- Is it a new model?
- The rice cookers?
- The rice cookers.
(This place is fake!)
(A fake by the production crew with a new rice cooker model?)
Come over here.
This place...
Customers would come...
- to try the rice.
- Totally.
It's all written there.
"Hangyeolmi rice, Yeonjin rice, and Goun rice,"
"with spicy stir-fried dishes."
"With salty grilled fish..."
The recommendations are all different.
(Rice pairings tailored to each order)
What's interesting is that there is only white rice. I wonder why.
Yes, Koreans love rice.
What's more,
rice tastes different...
- depending on the variety.
- True.
Gourmets are picky about it.
Such a company could totally exist.
- System.
- No, such a system could exist.
A restaurant like this must exist.
- Ji Hye, that wasn't it.
- What?
What she asked was why the rice was all white.
Is that so?
Why isn't there black or brown rice?
- Why no brown rice?
- Yes.
Don't tell us what you know.
- I also graduated from college.
- You're too impatient.
I'm a college graduate, okay?
Whether you graduated one or not doesn't matter.
Do you have an educational background complex?
No, I don't.
- You don't need one.
- I only shared what I knew.
- The information.
- She's a college graduate.
- Hi.
- This is all so interesting.
- Right.
How did you start a restaurant that serves rice?
- While preparing to change jobs, - Yes?
I came across the rice sommelier certificate.
- Rice sommelier?
- Yes.
While studying for it,
I found out about the various types of rice in Korea.
- It was a surprise.
- Right.
I thought a restaurant...
centered around rice would attract people's attention,
so I opened one.
Where did you earn...
- the certificate?
- In Japan.
- Her certificate is over there.
- Is it?
- Really?
- Yes. It caught my eye...
while walking in here, so I looked closely at it.
I earned the certificate in 2018.
- She got certified.
- In 2018.
If that's fake, it's document forgery.
It's indeed document forgery.
It's not fake.
(It's not fake.)
How many varieties of rice are there?
We have ten at the moment.
Ten.
(10 rice varieties brought in from all across the country)
Customers will come...
only if the rice tastes good,
so I'm very particular about the quality of the rice.
(The quality of rice matters the most!)
At first, I traveled across the country,
tried the rice, and bought it in person.
I buy rice that was milled that same day...
and manage the inventory so that I use it...
within two weeks.
Do you know the rice buffet place in Yeongdeungpo?
(Word has spread on social media...)
(about how delicious the rice tastes!)
I use up about 12kg to 13kg of rice per day.
The monthly sales are about 12,000 dollars.
Sixth Sense crew, is this place real?
(Sixth Sense crew, is this place real?)
I have a question.
Is that the price including the rice?
Yes. Order a side dish, and the rice is free.
- Really?
- Free?
It's really...
- This place is unbelievable.
- That's amazing.
That's amazing.
Would this price work...
for someone running a restaurant?
- Right?
- So...
- It's impossible.
So you see many unfamiliar rice varieties, right?
- Yes.
- When there's a new variety,
we promote it or hold an event.
At times, the rice is provided at a low price.
If the rice doesn't weigh the amount after packaging,
I buy it cheaply.
- To balance it out...
- She seems like the owner.
(Is this place real?)
(The owner handles even the tough questions with ease.)
Ma'am, can we have you taste the rice...
and guess what variety of rice...
- it is?
- You're a rice sommelier.
Even if I'm a rice sommelier,
it's hard to guess the variety...
- Is it?
- just by trying it.
After all, it's white rice.
But since you're asking, I'll do it.
- Let's do a few.
- Go get some, guys.
- We'll scoop five.
- Okay.
(They'll test 5 varieties of rice.)
Let's all stand here to confuse her.
(Maximum security)
Don't worry too much, ma'am.
(Full of pressure)
- What do I do?
- But...
But visually speaking, the rice looks all the same.
Right? And the aroma...
(Sniffing)
It smells just like regular rice.
(The rice looks completely identical on the outside.)
Try a bit of them.
Stop eating, will you?
I'm trying them, and they're so good.
All right. These five varieties.
(The five are all different varieties of rice.)
I'll take it slowly, first smelling it,
and then observing the color.
- Take your time.
- This is so unexpected.
There's no need to rush.
Even if she's a sommelier...
I'm amazed right now.
This is nerve-racking.
It can't be helped.
(Checking the aroma after trying it)
(Even the crew is nervous.)
This feels like...
Songhyangmi rice.
Correct.
(She got it in one go.)
(How did she know?)
This is amazing!
Songhyangmi rice has a sophisticated scent.
It's the most expensive rice.
I think she really is a rice sommelier.
Right?
(She first tastes the next rice again.)
I've never smelled this kind of rice before.
(Sniffing)
Why are you smelling your armpit?
(Why the armpit? I'm just curious.)
She's smelling her own skin to...
I do it to reset my nose...
- It resets your nose.
- Yes, this helps me smell better.
Smelling myself neutralizes my senses.
What happens if you smell my skin?
(Disgusted)
- So...
- What happens if you smell my skin?
(Forget me "Letter" by Chae Jeong An)
Great joke, Jeong An.
Keep up the good work!
- Great joke.
- It really was.
(She focuses again despite the sabotage.)
I know this one.
I think it's short-grain rice.
(Did she really get it right this time too?)
- Correct!
- You got it.
(Easily gets 2 in a row)
I can't believe it.
It smells like popcorn.
Popcorn? Is it buttery?
She's right!
(She sniffs it like she was taught.)
It really smells different.
(Sniffing)
(Tilting)
(She takes one careful bite,)
(then keeps smelling without answering.)
This is either Dalhami or Yeonjin rice.
But I'm not sure.
(He peeks at the answer.)
(Amazed)
(The answer was Yeonjin rice, just like she said!)
(The fact that she's even torn is surprising to them.)
I don't think I'll get this one right.
- I want to say Dalhami rice.
- Dalhami?
- Am I wrong?
- Let's see.
- It was Yeonjin rice.
- Yeonjin!
But you said it was either Dalhami or Yeonjin!
- I got chills when you said it!
- Me too!
We'll put it down as Yeonjin.
That's good!
Don't worry.
Is this Yudel rice?
- Correct.
- Gosh!
Dalhami rice?
- Dalhami!
- Correct!
(Her final score is 4 out of 5!)
Look, I got chills!
Did someone mouth the answer to her?
(I can't believe it!)
I get the feeling you really are a rice sommelier.
But now I'm curious.
How different can these varieties of rice be?
- Should we go get some?
- Sounds great.
I'm going to go with Songhyangmi rice first.
Songhyangmi rice is the fancy one, right?
Yes, I wanted to try it.
I'll be a consistent person.
- Hangyeolmi rice!
- I pick Hangyeolmi rice.
(Kyung Pyo goes with Hangyeolmi.)
I can't pick one. There are so many choices.
Can I try two types of rice?
Yes, you can.
You should go for it.
That's why I only got a little of the first one I chose too.
Not bad, right?
I need to try this Songhyangmi rice first.
(Jae Seok tries the rice first.)
(Impressed)
(Nodding furiously)
Songhyangmi rice is a little sticky.
It's really glossy, unlike the others.
(You can see its stickiness from when you scoop the rice.)
Songhyangmi is delicious.
This is really good rice.
(BIBI tries a bite of Songhyangmi too.)
(Startled)
(Exclaiming)
- Amazing.
- It's so good.
This Songhyangmi rice is so good!
(Eyes widening)
Gosh!
I can taste butter from Songhyangmi!
- Right? It's so flavorful.
- I can taste butter!
I also get a mushroom scent.
I noticed too!
(Songhyangmi has a soft mushroom scent as well.)
I love that it's chewy.
- It's sticky and nice.
- Exactly.
(Songhyangmi gives more mushroom scent the more you chew.)
(BIBI takes a big bite of rice with kimchi.)
- Goodness!
- It's amazing.
(Opening wide)
It's so good. This is crazy.
(Another bite)
We might finish our meal with rice alone!
The side dishes are great too.
Good rice is delicious even with just kimchi.
Of course.
- The mackerel is here!
- Mackerel!
The seaweed soup looks great.
It says Songhyangmi goes great with mackerel.
We just grill our mackerel without seasoning.
Then it goes perfectly with the rice flavor.
(You can't go wrong with mackerel and seaweed soup.)
I love mackerel! This is perfect!
This place is...
incredible!
Eun I, you're great with deboning fish!
Yes, I'm cutting it up into chunks for you all.
It's better than taking a little at a time.
- Now you can dip it in the sauce...
- This restaurant is my type.
- Right.
- I really love...
- not doing anything when eating.
- I know.
Obviously, I know.
- I love talking and only talking.
- How can I forget?
My wife, Kyung Eun, always nags me.
I know. Kyung Eun puts up with so much.
- Yes, she does.
- Kyung Eun does so much.
I'm best friends with Kyung Eun.
- Really?
- Yes.
What did she say about her husband?
Well...
(What did Yu Jae Seok's wife say about him?)
She doesn't say anything bad. She really respects her husband.
- That's nice.
- It really is.
And what a great parent!
- I actually...
- Who? Him?
- No.
- No, Na Kyung Eun.
Right.
- It's Kyung Eun.
- How silly of me.
- Kyung Eun is a great parent.
- Yes.
She's so good with children,
I got a lot of help from her too.
- You don't say.
- It's true.
I think she made the seaweed soup herself.
- Is it good?
- Yes, you should try.
(A sip of seaweed soup)
You make good seaweed soup too, Ji Hye.
Gosh, this is so deep.
- Isn't it?
- Yes, it's delicious.
(The deep flavor of seaweed after boiling for a long time)
(Jeong An tries a sip of soup too.)
Everything here is so good!
Gosh.
The soup is great too.
The mackerel is divine.
- It's amazing.
- Isn't it?
Yes!
(A thick chunk of mackerel on warm rice)
This is unbelievable.
- Excuse me.
- The soup is so rich.
Thank you!
Stir-fried pork!
(Doenjang stew, a bowl of rice's best friend)
We put just a little doenjang in the stew...
and braise it down.
Then it goes well with the flavorful rice.
(Flavorful rice and doenjang)
(To top it off, glossy and juicy...)
This is going to be awesome.
(stir-fried pork with a spicy kick)
I'd love to have this restaurant in my neighborhood.
I'd come here every day!
(BIBI mixes doenjang stew with rice first.)
(Taking a bite)
(Exclaiming)
The stew is amazing.
Everything here is delicious!
Workers are going to love this meal.
The pork is so good too!
I think I'll come here again on my own.
What?
- Right?
- I live close by too.
(Nodding)
This is a great restaurant.
- Exactly.
- It's amazing.
Workers will come here for lunch.
(He empties his bowl into his mouth.)
(Glancing)
(Glancing again)
- Hyeong Seo, can I...
- Sure, here you go.
- This is Jungwonjinmi rice.
- Thanks.
(He steals BIBI's Jungwonjinmi rice.)
(He finishes it in one bite,)
(then glances again.)
- Could I finish that, actually?
- Go ahead!
What's up?
He asked for some of my rice, so I gave him some.
But just now he asked if he could take all of it.
Our Kyung Pyo is letting loose again!
(Kyung Pyo Gone Wild: Part 2)
I just realized it's unlimited.
- That's right!
- This place is...
(Can 10 types of unlimited rice be real?)
(Pondering)
But the commissary fee is high here.
- Commissary fee?
- No, I meant...
(Commissary fee?)
(Questioning his ears)
- Are we in a prison?
- No, look!
I meant the leftover fee!
- What?
- You said commissary fee...
I don't know why that slipped out.
I've been looking at that sign.
It's five dollars per person.
You're saying this is real, right?
Exactly.
Say the fee was two dollars. That's too little.
But five dollars sounds like a real fine.
(A realistic leftover fee of 5 dollars)
- Goodness!
- It's here!
Thank you!
(Their extra order, ham and fried eggs, is here.)
- Ma'am?
- Yes?
How long has it been since you opened?
Since May of last year.
- Last year.
- It hasn't been that long.
Did you buy those cookers recently?
Oh, those...
(They first suspected the new cookers when they got here.)
(What's the story behind the newest model cookers?)
I used to have cookers from all different brands before.
- That was before.
- Did you get them for this show?
- No, but they got them for me.
- I see.
- Am I allowed to say?
- No, I get it.
That makes sense. Is this product placement?
They were brand new.
Yes, that's why I was suspicious.
When they offered, I said thank you...
and told them not to take them back!
(A cute and honest confession)
She's so adorable.
- That's so...
- Enjoy.
(She runs away after her shy confession.)
(Thank you, CUCHEN!)
With this restaurant...
- I really can't tell.
- Me neither.
And I hope this isn't fake.
When she explained everything,
I thought it was fake because it seemed memorized.
But after she got all the rice right...
- Exactly.
- It was incredible.
- She's so passionate!
- Right.
The way she treats her rice.
But the prices here...
I don't think you can make a profit.
- Right? It's too cheap.
- Yes.
But wait...
For workers who have to eat out,
these prices seem reasonable enough.
- Any higher, people won't come.
- Right.
It's hard to get lunch for ten dollars these days.
That's true.
Even a cup of coffee is seven dollars.
That's because you live in a rich neighborhood.
(Sighing)
(Chortling)
You both!
Is this how you treat a friend?
I have to agree with Jeong An on this one.
- Affordable coffee?
- Seven dollars?
That's way too expensive.
But the place I go to...
is a Blue Ribbon cafe.
You know where, right?
You know the Blue Ribbon Survey?
I could get a seven-dollar coffee...
- if I wanted to at my age!
- I mean...
Ji Ah... Sorry, Ji Hye...
Did you call me Ji Ah?
You spit out some rice, Jae Seok!
As you get older, you have to swallow before talking.
(Dizzy)
Your gums are weak, so your food gets everywhere.
I just can't...
But that was good.
(Jeong An is good.)
That was another great joke.
Goodness.
The owner here looks like a grain of rice.
- I see it too.
- She has a rice vibe.
Her face is fair and round.
(Sixth Sense crew, do I look like a rice?)
- What does Jae Seok look like?
- Rice vibe.
Doesn't he look like a millet?
I flinched a little.
I thought you were cursing.
- A millet!
- Oh, of course not.
- No, a millet! Not the curse word.
- No?
- The small, tiny grain!
- A millet.
- I really...
- You don't like it?
Millet Yu Jae Seok.
You don't like millets?
- No, I like it.
- Millet Jae Seok!
I'll have millet from now on.
(Laughing)
You look excited, BIBI.
She's the happiest I've seen on this shoot!
(Giggling)
- That's so you.
- I knew it.
- The dark IU.
- Evil IU.
We still have the third place.
- Let's go.
- We can compare.
(Low prices around 10 dollars A realistic leftover fee)
(An owner who's passionate about rice)
- I hope the last place has sweets.
- I'd love some dessert.
That'll make the perfect day.
- Is it a cafe?
- It'll be desserts, right?
(Is the last place a dessert place?)
Men's hair and barber?
- What's this?
- The bubbles must've been shampoo.
You're right.
(Was the mysterious bubble sound shampoo?)
Bubbles...
The last one must be beauty.
That means there's no dessert.
(Wailing)
That really would've hit the spot.
I was ready for some meringue cookies!
(Who's the last owner who's serious about "Mi?")
What is this place?
(Glancing)
This is a barbershop.
It smells like a set.
(An ordinary barbershop...)
- How suspicious.
- Yes.
- It looks like a set.
- Very.
(with set-like props)
This looks too simple.
- Should we meet the owner first?
- Right.
Hello?
- Hello?
- Nice to meet you!
- Hello.
- Hi.
- Good afternoon!
(He's speaking Japanese?)
(Why is he speaking Japanese?)
- Are you Japanese?
- Yes, I am!
I see!
I'm a hairstylist in Japan who goes by...
Crazy Karaya.
- Crazy Karaya.
- Crazy Karaage... Karaya.
Karaya.
- Mr. Karaya.
- Karaya.
Excuse me. There's an interpreter right here.
- Right!
- We were just excited.
I run a hair salon in Japan...
as Crazy Karaya.
This isn't his actual shop.
You just need to see if he's real.
So what we need to do now...
is to see whether he's lying or not.
That means he could pull a prank on us.
Excuse me, but how old are you?
I'm 42.
(Gasping)
- You're 42?
- What?
How long have you been doing this?
- 22 years.
- What? 22 years?
- 22 years?
- What?
He's been doing this for 22 years!
Why are you all reacting in Japanese?
(What?)
We're helping him feel at home.
Haven't you seen any Japanese shows?
Come on!
(Exclaiming)
This is basic!
Where in Japan do you work?
- In Osaka.
- Osaka!
Is there a special way you cut...
or style people's hair?
I have my own unique dyeing technique.
I paint the dye onto my hand...
- Hand?
- then place it on the hair.
With your hand?
The dye on your hand?
Hello, I'm Crazy Karaya!
I currently run a hair salon...
in Osaka, Umeda.
I'm quite good with colorful and flamboyant hair dyes.
(Very flashy)
At first, I wanted to try different designs...
for dyeing short hair.
And I thought it'd be fun to have a handprint as a design.
But that really blew up.
(His ultimate skill is coming up soon.)
Sixth Sense crew,
am I real?
He's saying a model is here to demonstrate.
Should we ask them to come out?
- Okay.
- Hi!
(A hair model that will help demonstrate the dyeing technique)
- Nice to meet you.
Hello, nice to meet you.
Are you Japanese too?
- Are you Japanese?
- No, he's Korean.
Why'd you reply in Japanese, then?
(Feeling tricked)
What a prankster!
Why did you speak Japanese in the first place?
I said it, and he replied!
So I thought he was Japanese!
(He's just an outgoing person!)
- Look!
- It's going straight to his hand.
(Meanwhile, Mr. Karaya starts to put dye on his hand.)
People usually use a brush.
- Right.
- Exactly.
(Dyeing with his hand, not a brush?)
I think the model would be nervous too.
Really?
Are you okay, sir?
(Calm)
Do you think he's a Japanese comedian?
Osaka is well-known...
- for its comedians.
- That's right.
But he just might be a fun person.
(BIBI thinks he might be a comedian from Osaka.)
Okay.
- Okay.
- Good.
(He got ready to start in the meantime.)
- No way.
- How does that even work?
- Are you good?
- Yes.
- Is he just stamping?
- I think so.
(Nervous for some reason)
(He stamps his hand after painting dye on it?)
Oh, so it's a handprint!
(A clear handprint on his head)
That's Wilson!
- Wilson!
- It's uncanny.
- It looks exactly like Wilson!
- Wilson!
- You're right.
- Yes.
- It does look pretty.
- But what about...
I use a brush to...
(He paints the empty spots with a brush.)
(In awe)
The handprint is unique.
- It's pretty!
- How nice.
It's like art.
(Exclaiming)
Are your customers satisfied with the result?
Most of them are very pleased, yes.
(The handprint dye is all the rage.)
But is that all?
(Nodding)
Is this it? Is it over?
(The handprint dye is finished after shampooing.)
So the handprint is dyed onto your hair.
What about feet?
It kind of looks like someone hit you.
- His foot on someone's head?
- What?
She said, "What about feet?"
You can't put feet on someone's head.
(You can do it gently!)
(Is this handprint dye real?)
It's like modern art.
But do you think this'll be in demand?
Forget that, I think he's ripping people off.
I don't think you should interpret that.
Please don't.
Please, don't do it.
How much is this, then?
The handprint dye with the bleaching and dyeing beforehand...
is around 220 dollars.
Really?
- 220 dollars.
- It's 220 dollars.
- 220 dollars?
- He bleaches too.
- I see.
- Including that. Okay.
And there's the added price for the design.
Apart from the dyeing technique,
I have one more special skill.
What is it?
It's called face shampoo.
- Face shampoo?
- Face shampoo.
Like a massage?
No, a face shampoo.
So he washes your face?
Remember, bubbles were part of our clue.
- That's right!
- Yes!
I remember.
(A hint filled with sounds of bubbles)
(Bubbling noise)
So this is the real deal.
(What could face shampoo mean?)
A face massage. I'm curious.
Does anyone want to try?
Would it wash off our makeup?
- Do you want to try?
- Wouldn't it wash it off?
Really? You think so?
I think I should do it, then.
- Everyone's got makeup on.
- Thank you, Kyung Pyo.
I'm honored to have such a handsome man as a customer.
(Handsome man, Ko Kyung Pyo)
Kyung Pyo loves the fans!
(Too nervous to hear)
This feels bad.
Why am I so scared?
What kind of massage is this?
But in the hint, there was someone...
- gurgling underwater.
- Right?
- How does this work?
- But he's really skilled...
with the preparation.
Okay.
- Okay.
- Good.
- I'm not facing the mirror, so...
- Are you nervous?
- Don't be nervous. It's okay.
- Okay.
- Don't worry.
- I don't know how this will begin.
Right, you can't see.
First, I wet the hair.
Oh, he wets the hair too.
He must massage the entire head.
Above the neck.
Right, the entire head.
The way he's spraying...
- is effortless.
- He's done this a lot.
- Right?
- Definitely.
- So he must work in this industry.
- I think so.
He looks professional.
Now, I wet the face as well.
(Chuckling)
Kyung Pyo, hold your breath.
(An impromptu Waterbomb Festival)
(The Korean Joker returns)
That can get in your nose sometimes!
- I'm scared.
- It's better than...
- That's real shampoo!
- Shampoo.
Something's happening.
Don't tell me he's washing my face with shampoo.
Soap might get into your nose. Brace yourself.
(A furious scalp massage)
This must feel refreshing and nice.
But why is this...
Isn't he just getting his hair washed while sitting up?
I've never seen anyone shampooed sitting straight up.
Are you okay?
Is it okay for us to just watch this?
- I feel bad for Kyung Pyo.
- He must've...
spent a lot on his hair today.
(It looks no different from regular shampoo.)
He must've spent a lot on his hair today.
Okay.
(Vigorous scrubbing)
(Shocked)
(The one who was feeling bad just a second ago)
Oh, no.
- But this is...
- Okay!
Hey, Kyung Pyo.
Kyung Pyo.
(Flying foam...)
(and the scent of shampoo)
What's going on?
Kyung Pyo...
(They can't take their eyes off the unbelievable sight.)
- Are you okay?
- What is going on?
- This is a lie. It's fake.
- Are you okay?
This can't be real. It's a lie.
He must be a comedian.
- He must be a comedian.
- This isn't normal.
A face massage, too.
- Kyung Pyo.
- Yes.
He's washing your face with shampoo.
- This is...
- Now...
(Rubbing the nose)
(Enthusiastic)
(Another world)
This is a lie.
I can't keep my senses straight.
- Are you okay?
- Kyung Pyo, this is entertaining.
- Kyung Pyo.
- The thing is,
- I can't hear very well.
- He can't hear.
- His ears are clogged.
- His ears are...
filled with thick foam.
This is...
(Laughing)
Gosh, this is...
(Gathering the foam from his hair)
The interpreter here is...
- The foam?
- It looks like Teletubbies.
It looks like Teletubbies.
(Total chaos)
(Rubbing the thrown foam right back in)
He looks skilled.
(Encore performance)
(I'm going to make your eyes sting.)
- Come on.
- This is fake.
- This makes no sense.
- It is.
- This is fake.
- This must be fake.
- We got it.
- Even to me, this looks fake.
Even if this feels good at first,
- it might not feel good later.
- Exactly.
(Whatever they say, he's just working hard.)
This is the funniest you've been since doing variety shows.
(A true variety show star)
- Are you okay?
- I'm fine.
Are you all right? That's nice.
(Cheerful guy Ko Kyung Pyo)
Does he have to go rinse off the soap himself?
Kyung Pyo, they say you have to go wash it off yourself.
I have to wash it myself?
I don't even know what state I'm in right now.
So this is how I look?
(Finally facing his own reflection)
(Why is our Actor Ko pushing himself this hard?)
This is insane.
How much is this face shampoo?
The face shampoo is around 40 dollars.
He burned through a lot of energy, too.
- Really?
- Thank you anyway.
- Thank you.
- My pleasure.
(Is the Japanese owner's face shampoo really authentic?)
Are you all right, Kyung Pyo?
Foam got into my ears. Could you help get it out?
Here? I should wipe your ears here.
I'm glad I stepped up.
You did a great job.
If Ji Hye had done this, it would've been hilarious.
It would've topped my crying-smiling acting.
Another legendary meme...
- would've been born.
- It would've created a new meme.
- What a shame.
- That's all for today.
- If Ji Hye had done this...
- If Ji Hye stepped up...
It would've been wild.
There'll be another good chance next time.
Anyway, I don't think you could do this at a hair salon.
Lathering hair and face together...
with the same product is impossible.
- And isn't it way too expensive?
- It is.
If you think of it as an art piece, it kind of makes sense.
Because no one has ever tried it.
(A plausible price because no one has tried it?)
How did it feel while being shampooed?
- It was quite bewildering, but...
- I understand.
- But this is...
- You look tired now.
But I'm not sure.
The way he touched my hair...
and the way his assistant...
washed my hair over there felt so...
- Did it feel genuine?
- It did.
- Shall we head out now?
- Yes.
Let's go.
(A salon owner who's serious about beauty)
(Unique styling and performance, yet an expensive price?)
(His skillful touch? A comedian from Osaka?)
- This is tricky as always.
- This is hard.
- I have no idea.
- I don't know.
(Time for the final decision)
We need to settle it here now.
What do we do?
Let's freely share our thoughts first.
Kyung Pyo, what do you think?
I think the third one is fake.
- Are you saying that out of spite?
- I am.
- He's upset.
- Come to think of it...
- You're upset.
- Because you're upset?
I feel like I've been made a fool of.
- Your energy dropped after that.
- Yes.
He's upset.
Jeong An, what do you think?
(What is Jeong An's choice?)
Actually,
watching Kyung Pyo do that at the third store,
I thought it was absurd.
- Right.
- It's so obvious that it's fake.
I actually think that's the trap.
The owner is real. Kyung Pyo's face is looking better.
(Fresh and soft face)
Seriously, he's getting prettier.
- The puffiness in his face is gone.
- He's getting prettier?
I think it's the first place. The tripe place.
It'd be hard for the owner to strike a balance...
and sing so confidently.
- It's hard even for a pro singer.
- It is hard to sing while cooking.
Right.
(A special place where he sells sweet tripe...)
(and sings delicious tunes)
(A system seen for the first time)
(You can add a song to your tripe order.)
(A live performance to enjoy while eating)
(Exciting)
(No. 1, the Singing Do-Re-Mi Owner)
- What do you think, Eun I?
- I think...
it's the tripe place.
- The tripe place?
- Yes.
- Ji Hye?
- I think two places are fake.
- It's just 1 place.
- There's only 1.
One place?
Snap out of it.
She's full of suspicion.
I'm serious. Here's why.
The tripe place Eun I mentioned seems fake, too,
but looking at the second place,
I thought there was no way to turn a profit...
without dinner service.
And if they really served so many varieties of rice,
we would already know about it.
- No way we wouldn't know.
- Because words would spread?
Yes.
(An owner obsessed with rice...)
(who opened a restaurant with her crazy love for rice)
(As many as 10 varieties...)
(of regional rice)
(It's a rice buffet where you order one dish and try all kinds of rice.)
(The rice tastes like butter.)
(It hit the spot for the Sixth Sense crew.)
(No. 2, an owner who's serious about rice)
You all seem to share similar views.
The last one actually...
- feels real.
- Right.
I think the answer is 1 of the 2.
One of the restaurants.
So this is...
Is the answer in here? Among what we said?
- Sure.
- Of course.
We named all three.
Seriously...
There has to be an answer to end this.
You two really never listen to others.
You two are truly incredible.
(Laughing)
We have to change, Jeong An.
We have to work on this now. Otherwise, we can't be on TV shows.
- This is new.
- People wouldn't cast us.
We have to make a decision now. We'll lock in our answer.
- Let's follow their opinions.
- The guests' opinions.
- The two of us?
- Yes.
Really?
Let's decide between numbers 1 and 2.
You picked number two, right?
Honestly, I'm confused. They both seem fake.
- Still...
- It's up to you.
You seem a bit smarter than me.
- Then should I decide?
- Yes.
- All right then.
- Choose number one.
Since everyone overall...
- suspected the tripe place, - Yes.
I'll choose the tripe place.
- The tripe place?
- Yes.
- All right.
- Let's watch the answer clip.
We chose number one, the tripe place.
(Revealing the answer clip)
(Today's theme!)
(Captivating everyone with beauty)
- It was tough.
- It really was.
- It's difficult.
- But I'll go with the tripe place.
The tripe place.
But the rice buffet...
(Fascinating everyone)
We've rarely guessed right two times in a row.
- Right.
- It almost never happened.
(If you get it wrong, it will drive you crazy, right?)
- Please!
- Please.
What is the only fake place?
(What is the only fake place?)
Please.
(Please let it be No. 1!)
Please!
(What is the only fake place?)
Is it number three?
(No. 1)
Which one is fake?
(Praying for a two-in-a-row correct guess)
(What is the only fake place?)
The tripe place?
Which is it?
(Our choice is No. 1!)
What is it?
(What is the only fake place?)
The tripe place?
Which is it?
(Our choice is No. 1!)
What is it?
(What is the only fake place?)
- Is it the rice buffet?
- Oh, no!
(The owner who's serious about rice is fake.)
- Is it the rice buffet?
- Oh, no!
I wanted to choose number two.
(I wanted to choose number 2.)
(No!)
(Frozen)
I said it was number two.
- The rice buffet?
- I said it was number two.
How is it fake? I mean, how much of this is fake?
(What on earth is this rice buffet?)
(Per capita rice consumption hit an all-time low last year.)
(Per capita rice consumption fell even more sharply last year.)
Right, people don't eat much rice these days.
(Per capita rice consumption has consistently dropped...)
(for the past 40 years.)
(Due to the problem, there are growing fears...)
(over a sharp plunge in rice prices.)
(So we visited the farms in person.)
I'm 28 now,
- Since he was 20?
- so I've farmed for 8 years.
I've been farming for about 30 years now.
I hope people will crave rice more...
once they taste delicious rice.
I hope it gets promoted widely.
So that's why they brought rice...
They got it from all over the nation like this?
(Rice brought all the way to Seoul from across the country)
(Then what was this place originally?)
Is that restaurant real?
- So it was originally a buffet?
- It was a buffet.
- Right. I said it was an eatery!
- You said it was a buffet.
I said it was a Korean food buffet!
I should've picked it...
just like I said earlier!
(Starting with the signboards)
This was the easiest one to set up.
(Adding two spoonfuls of detail)
(The fake rice buffet is complete.)
(Then...)
(Are all 10 types of rice real?)
Is this fake, too?
They probably just cooked rice on different settings!
No way.
- I bet this is real.
- Don't tell me this was all fake...
and we made a huge fuss over nothing.
(Yudel, Banggeut, Goun, short-grain Hangyeolmi, Songhyangmi)
The rice was so delicious.
(What are the other 6 types of rice?)
- Is this fake?
- Are these all the same?
Is it all the same rice?
(The food team is dispatched to fool the Sixth Sense crew.)
The food team came.
They are back after a long time.
(Crafting fake rice varieties)
They say it's fake varieties!
I took photos of those earlier.
- I'd buy them later.
- Me too!
I took photos of the names.
(Fake rice saved in my phone)
(Condensed milk)
What's this?
- What?
- I knew it!
- I can't believe this.
Condensed milk?
(Unbelievable)
(Popcorn)
- Popcorn?
- We said it tasted like popcorn.
I said it tasted like butter!
- No wonder the rice was savory.
- I know!
(Condensed milk, smoked oil, pandan leaves, popcorn,)
(mushrooms, and butter)
- Seriously?
- I knew it.
I wondered how the rice could be so savory.
I know.
This is crazy.
Rather than getting the answer wrong,
eating fake rice feels more upsetting!
My goodness. They really did this?
The food there was really delicious.
(Then what is the fake owner's real identity?)
What?
(Visiting a place to reveal her true identity!)
(CUCHEN, a company indispensable from rice)
What? It's giving me the chills.
(Someone is cooking rice there.)
(Is she the owner who's serious about rice?)
Who is she?
The owner?
(What is she doing here?)
Hello, I am Lee Mi Young,
Chief Researcher at Cuchen Rice Lab.
(The owner's true identity:)
(A researcher obsessed with rice, studying the ultimate rice taste)
This is unbelievable.
I got goosebumps.
We'll help you using this.
It's a rice cooker with a titanium inner pot.
It evenly distributes heat,
helping bring out the rice taste,
while adding a firm texture and savory aroma.
(They got the rice cooker needed for the restaurant!)
Then how did she guess the rice varieties?
(Then how did she guess the rice varieties?)
(She guessed even the fake varieties just by smell and taste alone.)
(It's fascinating. How did she know all that?)
(That's why she's a rice sommelier.)
- How did she do that?
- Right. This is it.
- She knew way too well.
- Right.
Did someone tell her?
This makes no sense.
- What's that?
- Was she wearing earphones?
(The owner's secret was...)
(It's hidden on her foot.)
Hidden on her foot?
(Smart watches?)
- Smart watches?
- What on earth is this?
- Seriously...
- What does that mean?
(She can distinguish to an extent as a rice sommelier.)
(Let's signal only the tricky ones!)
- They buzzed the watches?
- How?
It must be a lie.
(Left and right feet numbers are assigned for each rice bowl.)
(The rice tasting test a while ago)
(The answer is Yudel, made with condensed milk.)
Memorizing all that is impressive.
If she picks up the third rice on the right...
(Sending three vibrations via the smartwatches)
One, two, three... I can't believe this.
(This is...)
(The answer is Yudel.)
(Of course it's the right answer.)
(The vibration is insane.)
What's all this?
It's unbelievable.
- They're total scammers.
- Totally.
They're hustlers.
What happened?
I got so excited...
- and even yelled "Correct!"
- Correct!
- I got carried away.
- I know.
I was so impressed.
(To fool the Sixth Sense members,)
(she even practiced cooking rice with the brand-new pots!)
(Button On)
Cooking begins.
(She successfully captivated them with the best rice flavor.)
It's unbelievable.
(It's not over yet.)
Oh, no!
Today was way too difficult.
(Did you notice today's B-Side?)
What is it?
(The clues are always right around you.)
- Again?
- There were clues?
When was it?
Where?
It's a lie.
(The B-Side hidden in fake place menu)
I didn't see anything.
I checked everything earlier.
(The B-Side hidden in fake place menu)
(Takeout side dishes)
- Takeout side dishes?
Did you order takeout side dishes?
(The fake restaurant's side dishes you enjoyed so much)
(Kkakdugi, kimchi, salted squid, pickled perilla leaves, seaweed)
(Didn't they taste familiar somehow?)
- What's all this?
- I can't believe this.
Did you order takeout side dishes?
- I... Kyung Pyo.
- I thought... Gosh, Eun I.
- Help me up.
- No wonder it was so good.
We're the crew who contacted you earlier today.
- We're here to buy side dishes.
- Where is it? Gangnam?
(A BBQ place in Gangnam-gu)
- The BBQ place?
- Yes.
(Verified as Jae Seok's go-to spot)
I thought the doenjang stew was so good.
(The doenjang stew from Jae Seok's favorite spot)
(The next favorite restaurant?)
- Whose favorite restaurant is this?
- I know the place.
Does she come here often?
- Yes.
- That's right!
What? Which side dish did you get from this place?
- The seaweed.
- I see.
I didn't eat this.
I didn't eat this dish.
(Whose favorite restaurant is this?)
- Where is this place?
- This is where I go.
- My goodness.
- The mackerel and seaweed soup?
The seaweed soup was quite unique.
- Did you not notice it?
- Right.
I just said I liked it. It felt like my birthday.
Those side dishes are from my favorite place.
The salted squid!
(My seasoned chives.)
- Where is that place?
- It's unbelievable.
(That's how it was completed.)
- This is insane.
- Why do you go this far?
Sixth Sense members, this place is fake!
Stop smiling!
(The owner who is serious about rice is fake.)
(Eun I is sulky.)
(Collapsing)
What's truly amazing about her is, as we left...
and took a photo together, she asked if she could hang it...
- in the restaurant.
- Exactly.
- Right.
- She was the only one who did that.
- Exactly.
- So she was acting.
(May I hang the photo up here?)
(Kyung Pyo is a fool.)
(Today's best actress)
Why are you over there? You should act!
- She will make a great actress.
- You should be an actress,
not a researcher.
If she started an acting career, she'd be better than me.
- Show us.
- Show us, Ji Hye.
(Groaning)
How could this even happen?
(Lee Ji Hye's one-man show)
This is it. Hey, you nailed it right away.
- You pulled it off right away.
- I can do it right away.
(This is so funny.)
(As expected of the Korean Joker)
So, it turns out Kyung Pyo...
got an expensive massage.
That's true.
Thank you so much.
(My pleasure.)
- It's worth 40 dollars.
- Including the airfare,
getting the massage would've cost you quite a lot.
You're the winner today.
- Right.
- You're the winner.
Thank you so much.
(The one who enjoyed the face shampoo deserves to leave!)
One of our guests today is someone we're truly thankful for.
(A guest who was urgently cast at 10pm last night)
(That urgently?)
(Between Ye Na and Jun Ha, who's the one urgently cast?)
(I got a call that felt like something was wrong.)
(We're thankful that he came.)
(Jun Ha reunites with nostalgic MCs about 21 years after "Truth Game.")
(Getting emotional)
(It feels a bit different.)
(Believe it or not, we're on great terms.)
(Just looking at their faces, I know if they are fake or real.)
(How do you know?)
(I just can tell.)
(This makes no sense.)
(You can't run a business like this.)
(What, did you come to film "Alley Restaurant?")
(Why offer solutions everywhere we go?)
(He's a guest.)
(I'm going to catch them all today.)
Our Ye Na.
(Everyone is so into "Catch Catch.")
(How is Ye Na's catching sense?)
(You have to go strictly by vibe, feeling, and intuition.)
(Catch, catch)
(To me, this place seems the fakest of all.)
(Can you just say things like that?)
(How will the chemistry between Ye Na and Jun Ha end?)